{"questions":[{"question":"The primary purpose of the passage is to","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"reconcile two opposing theories"},{"key":"B","answer":"compare two different explanationsfor a phenomenon"},{"key":"C","answer":"describe experimental research that appears to support an unpopular theory"},{"key":"D","answer":"present evidence that may help to resolve an apparent contradiction"},{"key":"E","answer":"describe a hypothesis that has cause a controversy"}],"right":["D"],"parent":0},{"question":"It can be inferred from the passage that the author would most likely describe the \"additional evidence\" (line 12) providedby experiments with adrenergic antagonists as","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"revolutionary"},{"key":"B","answer":"disappointing"},{"key":"C","answer":"incomplete"},{"key":"D","answer":"unexpected"},{"key":"E","answer":"corroborative"}],"right":["E"],"parent":0},{"question":"The passage provides information about which of the following topics?","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"The mechanism by which glucose affects memory storage"},{"key":"B","answer":"The evidence that prompted scientist to test the effects of adrenaline on memory regulation"},{"key":"C","answer":"The reason that the effects of glucose on memory were tested"},{"key":"D","answer":"The ways that memory storage modifies the structure of the brain"},{"key":"E","answer":"The kinds of training used to test memory enhancement in rats"}],"right":["C"],"parent":0},{"question":"The author refers to the results of the experiment using adrenergic antagonists as \"negative findings\" (line 13) most likely because the adrenergic antagonists","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"failed to disrupt adrenaline's effect on memory"},{"key":"B","answer":"did not affect glucose's ability to enhance memory."},{"key":"C","answer":"did not block adrenaline's ability to increase blood glucose levels"},{"key":"D","answer":"only partially affected adrenaline's ability to enhance memory"},{"key":"E","answer":"disrupted both adrenaline's and glucose's effect on memory "}],"right":["B"],"parent":0},{"question":"Which of the following best describes the passage as a whole?","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"An outline for future research"},{"key":"B","answer":"An expanded definition of commonly misunderstood terms"},{"key":"C","answer":"An analysis of a dispute between two theorists"},{"key":"D","answer":"A discussion of research findings in an ongoing inquiry"},{"key":"E","answer":"A confirmation of an established authority's theory"}],"right":["D"],"parent":1},{"question":"According to the passage, Darley found that after seven months of kindergarten six year olds acquired which of the following abilities?","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"Differentiating between foreseeable and unforeseeable harm"},{"key":"B","answer":"Identifying with the perpetrator of a harmful action"},{"key":"C","answer":"Justifying harmful actions that result from provocation"},{"key":"D","answer":"Evaluating the magnitude of negative consequences resulting from the breaking of rules"},{"key":"E","answer":"Recognizing the difference between moral absolutism and moral autonomy"}],"right":["A"],"parent":1},{"question":"According to the passage, Piaget and Keasey would not have agreed on which of the following points?","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"The kinds of excuses children give for harmful acts they commit"},{"key":"B","answer":"The age at which children begin to discriminate between intentional and unintentional harm"},{"key":"C","answer":"The intentions children have in perpetrating harm"},{"key":"D","answer":"The circumstances under which children punish harmful acts"},{"key":"E","answer":"The justifications children recognize for mitigating punishment for harmful acts"}],"right":["B"],"parent":1},{"question":"It can be inferred that the term \"public duty\" (line 33) in the context of the passage, means which of the following?","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"The necessity to apprehend perpetrators."},{"key":"B","answer":"The responsibility to punish transgressors"},{"key":"C","answer":"An obligation to prevent harm to another"},{"key":"D","answer":"The assignment of punishment for harmful action"},{"key":"E","answer":"A justification for punishing transgressions"}],"right":["C"],"parent":1},{"question":"According to the passage, Keasey's findings support which of the following conclusions about six-year-old children?","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"They have the ability to make autonomous moral judgments."},{"key":"B","answer":"They regard moral absolutism as a threat to their moral autonomy."},{"key":"C","answer":"They do not understand the concept of public duty."},{"key":"D","answer":"They accept moral judgment made by their peers more easily than do older children."},{"key":"E","answer":"They make arbitrary moral judgments."}],"right":["A"],"parent":1},{"question":"It can be inferred form the passage that Piaget would be likely to agree with which of the following statements about the punishment that children under seven assign to wrongdoing?","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"The severity of the assigned punishment is determined by the perceived magnitude of negative consequences more than by any other factor."},{"key":"B","answer":"The punishment is to be administered immediately following the transgression."},{"key":"C","answer":"The children assign punishment less arbitrarily than they do when they reach the age of moral autonomy."},{"key":"D","answer":"The punishment for acts of unintentional harm is less severe than it is for acts involving accidental harm."},{"key":"E","answer":"The more developmentally immature a child, the more severe the punishment that the child will assign."}],"right":["A"],"parent":1},{"question":"According to the passage, the research of Nesdale and Rule suggests which of the following about five-yearold children?","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"Their reactions to intentional and accidental harm determine the severity of the punishments they assign."},{"key":"B","answer":"They, as perpetrators of harmful acts, disregard the feelings of the children they harm."},{"key":"C","answer":"They take into account the motivations of actions when judging the behavior of other children."},{"key":"D","answer":"They view public duty as a justification for accidental, but not intentional, harm."},{"key":"E","answer":"They justify any action that protects them from harm."}],"right":["C"],"parent":1}],"parent":["Although the hormone adrenaline is known to regulate\nmemory storage, it does not pass from the blood into brain\ncells. We are faced with an apparent paradox: how can a\nhormone that does not act directly on the brain have such a\n(5)large effect on brain function?\n Recently, we tested the possibility that one of the\nhormone's actions outside the brain might be responsible.\nSince one consequence of adrenaline release in an animal\nis an increase in blood glucose levels, we examined the\n(10)effects of glucose on memory in rats. We found that \nglucose injected immediately after training enhances memory\ntestedthe next day. Additional evidence was provided by\nnegative findings: drugs called adrenergic antagonists,\nwhich block peripheral adrenaline receptors, disrupted\n(15)adrenaline's ability to regulate memory but did not affect\nmemory enhancements produced by glucose that was not\nstimulated by adrenaline. These results are as they should\nbe if adrenaline affects memory modulation by increasing\nblood glucose levels.","The age at which young children begin to make moral\ndiscriminations about harmful actions committed against\nthemselves or others has been the focus of recent research\ninto the moral development of children. Until recently,\n(5)child psychologists supported pioneer developmentalistJean.\nPiaget in his hypothesis that because of their immaturity,\nchildren under age seven do not take into account the intentions of a person committing accidental or deliberate harm,\nbut rather simply assign punishment for transgressions on\n(10)the basis of the magnitude of the negative consequences\ncaused. According to Piaget, children under age seven\noccupy the first stage of moral development, which is characterized by moral absolutism (rules made by authorities\nmust be obeyed) and imminent justice (if rules are broken,\n(15)punishment will be meted out). Until young children mature,\ntheir moral judgments are based entirely on the effect\nrather than the cause of a transgression. However, in recent\nresearch, Keasey found that six-year-old children not only\ndistinguish between accidental and intentional harm, but\n(20)also judge intentional harm as naughtier, regardless of the\namount of damage produced.Both of these findings seem\nto indicate that children, at an earlier age than Piaget\nclaimed, advance into the second stage of moral development, moral autonomy, in which they accept social rules\n(25)but view them as more arbitrary than do children in the\nfirst stage.\n Keasey's research raises two key questions for developmental psychologistsabout children under age seven:do\nthey recognize justifications for harmful actions, and do\n(30)they make distinctions between harmful acts that are preventable and those acts that have unforeseen harmful consequences? Studies indicate that justifications excusing\nharmful actionsmight include public duty,self-defense, and\nprovocation. For example, Nesdale and Rule concluded that\n(35)children were capable of considering whether or not an\naggressor's action was justified by public duty: five year\nolds reacted very differently to \"Bonnie wrecks Ann's\npretend house\" depending on whether Bonnie did it \"so\nsomebody won't fall over it\" or because Bonnie wanted \"to\n(40)make Ann feel bad.\"Thus, a child of five begins to understand that certain harmful actions, though intentional, can\nbe justified; the constraints of moral absolutism no longer\nsolely guide their judgments.\n Psychologists have determined that during kindergarten\n(45)children learn to make subtle distinctions involving harm.\nDarley observed that among acts involving unintentional\nharm, six-year-old children just entering kindergarten could\nnot differentiate between foreseeable, and thus preventable,\nharm and unforeseeable harm for which the perpetrator\n(50)cannot be blamed. Seven months later, however, Darley\nfound that these same children could make both distinctions, thus demonstrating that they had become morally\nautonomous"]}